right good afternoon and welcome
下午好，欢迎光临
everybody welcome to the very badly
大家都非常欢迎
misquoted from Star Trek
从《星际迷航》中被错误引用
it's Java Jim but not as we know it
是Java Jim，但不是我们所知道的
because the original quote that people
因为原来的报价人
like to say is it's life Jim but not as
喜欢说这是吉姆的生活，但不是
we know it and that's actually a
我们知道这实际上是一个
misquote anyway but anyway the idea
无论如何都会引用错误，但是无论如何
behind this presentation is to talk
这个演讲的背后是谈论
about lambda expressions and so what
关于lambda表达式等等
I've done in terms of the agenda is
我已经完成的议程是
divided up into three parts
分为三部分
first part we're going to talk about the
第一部分，我们将讨论
details of lambda expressions so who
lambda表达式的详细信息是谁
here is using JDK 8 ok good so we'll
这里使用的是JDK 8，好的，所以我们将
talk a bit about the details of lambda
谈谈lambda的细节
expressions from the point of view of
从以下观点看
what they are and how you use in and so
它们是什么以及如何使用
on then we'll talk some about the
然后，我们将讨论一些有关
performance of lambda expressions
lambda表达式的性能
because the way that they're implemented
因为它们的实施方式
is not quite how you might expect it and
不完全是您所期望的
so there are some interesting details
所以有一些有趣的细节
that we can discuss when it comes to how
我们可以讨论何时
lambdas perform compared to the
lambdas与
equivalent anonymous inner classes and
等效的匿名内部类和
then the last part of the presentation
然后是演讲的最后一部分
is how far can we take lambdas this is
我们可以带lambdas多远
where we get into the it's Java Jim but
我们进入的是Java Jim，
not as we know it and the way that I've
不是我们所知道的和我的方式
kind of divided this up is that the
这种划分的一种是
first two parts are what I describe is
我描述的前两部分是
interesting and useful the last part is
有趣而有用的最后一部分是
interesting but not so useful because
有趣但不太有用，因为
nobody is going to program in Java the
没有人会用Java编程
way that I'm going to show you at the
我将向您展示的方式
end of this presentation if you do
如果您这样做，本演示文稿的结尾
you're doing it wrong right so let's
你做错了对吧，让我们
start then with lambda expressions now
然后从lambda表达式开始
since you're using JDK I eat you will be
因为您使用的是JDK，所以我会吃
aware of some of this stuff but it's
知道其中一些东西，但是
worth talking about this a little bit of
值得谈论一下
detail so what we had before jdk 8 was
细节，所以我们在jdk 8之前拥有的是
the idea of anonymous inner classes and
匿名内部类的思想和
what we could do there is we could
我们在那里可以做的是
create a reference to an instance of a
创建对一个实例的引用
class that implemented a particular
实现了特定的类
interface and in the case of this one
界面，在这种情况下
it's a anonymous in a class that has a
这是一个匿名类
single in a single method that needs to
单一方法需要
be implemented so rather than actually
如此实施而不是实际实施
having to either create a new class
必须创建一个新类
which implemented that in
这实现了
face and then instantiate it what we can
面对然后实例化它我们可以
do is we can simply say create my new
我们可以简单地说创建新的
runnable which is the interface and I
可运行的是接口和我
want the method of that interface to be
希望该接口的方法是
implemented this way by having run and
通过运行并以这种方式实现
then we're going to do some stuff and
然后我们要做一些事情，
then we'll start the the thread in the
然后我们将在
usual way problem with this is it's
通常的方式问题是
rather verbose because we have to
相当冗长，因为我们必须
express it explicitly state that the
明确表示，
interface we want to implement is
我们要实现的接口是
runnable we have to have brackets in
可运行的，我们必须在方括号中
there we have to explicitly put that the
我们必须明确地指出
method is called run it's a type void
方法称为运行，它是一个类型为void
return and then we have some stuff that
返回，然后我们有一些东西
we want to do so it's a lot of stuff in
我们想要这样做，其中有很多东西
there which we don't really need and
那里我们并不需要
that's what lambda expressions are all
那就是lambda表达式的全部
about it's it's a new style of doing
关于这是一种新的做事方式
that kind of thing but in a much simpler
这种事情，但简单得多
form so now we know that we can use a
表格，所以现在我们知道我们可以使用
lambda expression to do that so we have
lambda表达式可以做到这一点
a single line now where rather than
现在一行而不是
having all that extra stuff the compiler
有所有多余的东西编译器
infers from where we use that particular
从我们使用该特定位置的地方推断
lambda expression what the type is so
lambda表达式的类型是什么
the compiler knows that thread takes a
编译器知道线程需要一个
runnable as a parameter so it knows that
作为参数运行，因此它知道
the type it's going to have to create is
它必须创建的类型是
a runnable and then we tell it what the
一个可运行的，然后我们告诉它什么
implementation of that method is but
该方法的实现是
without explicitly saying what it
没有明确说出它是什么
returns what the parameters are and so
返回参数是什么，等等
on
上
so much much cleaner much much easier to
清洁得多，容易得多
use if we dig into a bit more detail
如果我们更详细地使用，请使用
about what that really means what we're
关于什么才真正意味着我们
doing here is having a simplified way of
在这里做的是一种简化的方法
representing behavior in Java rather
代表Java中的行为
than it being state we can assign
比我们可以分配的状态
behavior to a variable and we can pass
行为到变量，我们可以通过
behavior as a parameter to another
行为作为另一个参数
method so this has a lot of benefits in
方法，因此在
terms of what we want to do and in terms
我们想做的事情
of where we can use a lambda expression
我们可以在哪里使用lambda表达式
we can use a lambda expression anywhere
我们可以在任何地方使用lambda表达式
where the type that's it's going to
类型是什么
represent is a functional interface
表示是一个功能接口
functional interface is one which has
功能接口是具有
only one abstract method now prior to
现在只有一种抽象方法
JDK eight it was pretty easy to spot the
JDK八很容易发现
functional interface because it only had
功能接口，因为它只有
one method defined in it in JDK eight
JDK中定义的一种方法八
in addition to introducing Lander
除了介绍Lander
expressions there is the idea of static
表达式有静态的想法
methods and default methods in
中的方法和默认方法
interfaces what that means is that you
接口意味着你
now have behavior included in an
现在的行为包含在
interface and the kind of net effect of
界面和净效果的种类
that is that you have multiple
那就是你有多个
inheritance of behavior as well as
行为的继承以及
multiple inheritance of types because
类型的多重继承，因为
interfaces allow you to have multiple
介面可让您拥有多个
types associated with a variable what we
与变量相关的类型
don't have in Java is multiple
在Java中没有多个
inheritance of state so that's the
国家的继承，这就是
important thing it's not like C++ where
重要的是它不像C ++
you have true model inheritance Java
您拥有真正的模型继承Java
you've got multiple inheritance of types
你有多个类型的继承
multiple inheritance of behavior but not
行为的多重继承，但不是
multiple inheritance of state so in jdk
状态的多重继承因此在jdk中
8 if you have a single abstract method
8，如果您有一个抽象方法
then you can use a lambda expression to
然后您可以使用Lambda表达式
represent that and the key thing about
代表那个和关键的事情
that is that the body of the lambda
那就是lambda的身体
expression is the implementation of that
表达是那个的实现
single abstract method the other thing
单一抽象方法另一件事
about this was that in terms of the
关于这一点，就
design this is actually a much simpler
设计这实际上要简单得多
way of allowing people to have behavior
让人们有行为的方式
assigned to variables and passed as
分配给变量并作为
parameter rather than having to
参数，而不必
introduce a new functional type to the
向该功能引入新的功能类型
language because that that's another
语言，因为那是另一种
alternative way of doing it other
其他的替代方法
languages do have a true functional type
语言确实具有真正的功能类型
but in Java because it was a existing
但是在Java中，因为它已经存在
language they didn't want to add a new
他们不想添加新的语言
functional type so they've done it
功能类型，所以他们做到了
through the idea of lambdas so in terms
通过lambdas的想法
of the syntax of a lambda expression it
lambda表达式的语法
is like a method but very importantly it
就像一种方法，但非常重要的是
is not a method so it's not associated
不是一种方法，所以它没有关联
with a class that is a very significant
班级非常重要
point and we'll kind of come back to
点，我们会回到
that in a moment but a lambda expression
片刻之后，只是一个lambda表情
is a functional interface type it is not
是功能接口类型，不是
associated with a class in terms of the
与类别相关的
the syntax what we have is the left-hand
我们所拥有的语法是左手
side of the lambda operator are the
lambda运算符的一面是
parameters that we're passing to our
我们传递给我们的参数
method like object and the right hand
像对象和右手这样的方法
side is the body of our method like
侧面是我们方法的主体
object but not associated with the class
对象，但与类无关
so in terms of its structure it is very
所以就其结构而言
similar to a method so it has a set of
与方法类似，因此它具有一组
typed parameters it has body
它具有正文的键入的参数
return type and it can throw exceptions
返回类型，它可能引发异常
so all of those things are exactly the
所以所有这些都是
same as method but because it's not
与方法相同，但不是
associated with class we don't call it a
与课程相关的我们不称其为
method the other thing about this is
方法与此有关的另一件事是
that it is closure over values not
它是对价值的封闭而不是
closure over types what that means is
对类型的封闭意味着
that if you look at how you can use a
如果您看看如何使用
lambda expression you can reference
您可以参考的lambda表达式
variables from the surrounding scope so
来自周围范围的变量
you can reference variables from outside
您可以从外部引用变量
of the lambda expression and use those
并使用那些表达式
in your lambda expression but there is a
在你的lambda表达式中，但是有一个
restriction on that if you go back to
如果你回到
anonymous inner classes the way that you
匿名内部类的方式
could access variables in the
可以访问
surrounding scope was only if they were
周围的范围只有
marked explicitly as final so their
明确标记为最终，因此他们
value could be set once and you couldn't
值只能设置一次，而您不能
change it that way you couldn't change
以无法更改的方式进行更改
the the value inside the anonymous in a
匿名中的值
class with lambda expressions the same
与lambda表达式相同的类
thing applies but the rules have been
事情适用，但规则已经
relaxed a little bit so now the variable
放松一点，所以现在变量
has to be effectively final which means
必须有效地最终确定
that it can be marked final or if it's
可以将其标记为最终的，或者
not marked final it must behave as if it
没有标记为final，它必须表现得像
was so its value can only be set once
原来只能设置一次
and it cannot be changed right so let's
它无法正确更改，所以让我们
talk a little bit about capturing
谈谈捕捉
lambdas so a capturing lambda is one
lambda，所以捕获lambda是一个
which uses a variable from the
它使用来自
surrounding scope and when I started
范围和我何时开始
using lambdas I wrote a piece of code
使用lambdas我写了一段代码
which is very similar to this so I had a
这非常相似，所以我有一个
class which I called data processor it
我称之为数据处理器的类
had a current value int and then I
具有当前值int，然后我
wanted to process something so I used a
想处理一些东西，所以我用了
lambda expression and I did current
lambda表达式，我当前
value plus plus I compiled it I ran it
价值加我编译它我运行它
it did exactly what I wanted it to do I
它确实做了我想要的事情
thought yes great my code is good then I
以为是，我的代码很好，然后我
thought about it a little bit more I
我多想了一下
thought to myself hang on that shouldn't
我以为自己坚持不应该
work because current value is not
工作，因为当前值不是
effectively final now I've just told you
实际上，我刚刚告诉你
that we have closures over values not
我们对价值没有封闭
closures over types so how can that work
对类型的封闭，这如何工作
how can the compiler do what I don't
编译器如何做我不做的事情
expect it to do and it turns out I did a
期望它能做到，事实证明我做了一个
bit of digging on this it took me a
对此进行了一点研究
while to find out what was happening
找出正在发生的事情
turns out that the compiler does
原来编译器确实
something on your behalf I'm not
代表你的东西我不是
actually convinced that this is a good
实际上相信这是一个很好的选择
idea because what happens is it actually
想法，因为实际上发生了什么
inserts
插入
reference to this in front of your
在您面前引用此
variable now remember that a Lander
变量现在要记住，着陆器
expression is not associated with the
表达式与
class that's not like an anonymous in a
在课堂上不像匿名的类
class where there is an instance of that
有一个实例的类
anonymous in a class and if you use this
在课堂上匿名，如果您使用此
it would refer to the instance of that
它指的是那个
class under expression if you use this
使用此表达式时的类
it refers to the class of the
它指的是
surrounding scope in this case it would
在这种情况下，范围会
be the data processor so if we insert
是数据处理器，所以如果我们插入
this in front of current value this is
这是当前值前面的
an effectively final variable so we can
一个有效的最终变量，因此我们可以
then use the effectively final variable
然后使用有效的最终变量
we can indirectly access through that
我们可以通过它间接访问
into current value and we can increment
到当前值，我们可以增加
it so yes it's old was the problem for
所以是的，这是老问题了
us
我们
but I don't think we want the problem
但我不认为我们要这个问题
solved because the whole idea of lambda
解决了，因为整个lambda的想法
expressions is we're dealing with
表达式是我们正在处理的
functional programming where you
函数式编程
shouldn't be modifying state this allows
不应该修改状态，这允许
you getting away with modifying state
你摆脱修改状态
when you shouldn't really be doing it so
当你不应该这样做的时候
like I say I think this is a bit of a
就像我说的，我认为这有点
mmm bit of a if he called because also
嗯，如果他打电话，是因为
introduces code which you're not seeing
引入您看不到的代码
in the actual code that you write so
在你写的实际代码中
you're not aware of that reference being
你不知道那个参考是
inserted method references so this is
插入的方法引用，所以这是
the idea that where you have a lambda
你在哪里有lambda的想法
expression which is simply using a
表达式只是使用一个
method on the parameter that you're
参数的方法
passing to it or some other forms of
传递给它或其他形式的
that which we'll come to in a moment you
我们稍后会谈到的
can simplify that by eliminating some of
可以消除一些
the extra code so in this case I've got
额外的代码，所以在这种情况下，我有
a file filter X and I want to represent
文件过滤器X，我想代表
that using a lambda expression where I
使用lambda表达式的地方
take file F and I'm going to call the
拿文件F，我要打电话给
can read meth on can read method on F I
可以读取方法可以读取FI上的方法
can simplify that by simply saying file
只需说出文件即可简化
which is the tonic colon colon and then
这是补药结肠结肠，然后
can read and that's equivalent to the
可以阅读，相当于
lambda expression above in terms of the
上面的lambda表达式
the way that you can use method
使用方法的方式
references they're actually three
引用他们实际上是三个
distinct ways that you can use them in
在其中使用它们的独特方式
terms of forming them and so the idea of
形成它们的条件等等
the this is that you have a target
这是你有一个目标
reference double colon and then the
参考双冒号，然后
method name so the method names going to
方法名称，因此方法名称将
be caught on the target reference as I
我被目标参考所吸引
said there are three kinds of these one
说这三种
relates to static methods one is where
与静态方法有关之一是
you're calling an instance method
您正在调用实例方法
on an arbitrary type and one where
在任意类型上
you're calling an instance method on an
您正在调用一个实例方法
existing object and if we look at the
现有对象，如果我们看一下
rules for construction of those most of
那些大多数建筑的规则
it's fairly straightforward so in the
这非常简单，因此在
first case if we're dealing with a
第一种情况，如果我们正在处理
static method what you're gonna have is
静态方法您将拥有的是
a lambda expression where you've got
一个lambda表达式
some arguments and then you've got a
一些争论，然后你有一个
class name and then you call the static
类名，然后调用静态
method on that with those arguments so
这些参数的方法
to convert it into our method reference
转换成我们的方法参考
you simply use the class name double
您只需使用类名double
colon static method name great going to
冒号静态方法名称很棒
the bottom where we using an existing
我们使用现有的底部
object reference what we can do is same
对象引用我们可以做的是一样的
thing we can say okay we've got some
我们可以说的好吧，我们有一些
arguments we've got an expression which
参数，我们有一个表达式
represents an existing object we're
代表我们现有的对象
calling the instance method on that with
调用实例方法
the arguments so the way we construct
论据，所以我们构造的方式
the method reference is basically the
方法参考基本上是
same except rather than using the type
除了使用类型以外，其他均相同
we use the object reference one in the
我们在
middle is slightly more complicated
中间稍微复杂一些
because in this case we have a set of
因为在这种情况下，我们有一组
arguments where the first argument is
第一个参数是的参数
the type that we're going to call the
我们将称之为的类型
method on and then we have and
方法，然后我们有
potentially more arguments after that
在那之后可能会有更多的争论
and it's those rest of arguments which
这是其余的论点
we pass as arguments to the instance
我们作为参数传递给实例
method on the first argument type ok now
第一个参数类型的方法现在确定
that all looks very complicated so I
一切看起来都很复杂，所以我
show you some examples and it makes it
给你看一些例子，它使它成为现实
much clearer at least I hope it does so
至少我希望它更清晰
the first calling a static method we've
第一次调用静态方法
got string s as our parameter and we
将字符串s作为我们的参数，我们
calling integer dot parseint on s so
在s上调用整数点parseint
very simple we can convert that into a
非常简单，我们可以将其转换为
method reference by saying integer
说整数的方法引用
double colon parse int the second one is
双冒号解析int第二个是
where things a little bit more
事情多一点
complicated so we've got string s and
复杂，所以我们有字符串s和
we've got into buyers parameters and
我们已经了解了买家参数，
what we want to actually do an embodied
我们想要实际实现的
of the lambda expression is say s dot
lambda表达式的意思是说点
substring of I and we can convert that
我的子字符串，我们可以将其转换为
into a method reference by using string
使用字符串转换为方法引用
because that's the type of the first
因为那是第一种
argument S and call substring on that
参数S并在其上调用子字符串
which will pass I as the parameter to
这会将I作为参数传递给
the call and then in terms of the last
通话，然后就最后一个而言
one if we've got an existing object if
一个，如果我们有一个现有的对象，如果
we want in this case we've got an axis a
我们希望在这种情况下，我们有一个轴a
and then we're going to call get length
然后我们打电话给获取长度
which is in the class which we're
这是我们所在的班级
actually running in we can use this as a
实际运行中，我们可以将其用作
reference because again the lambda
参考，因为再次lambda
expression is not associated with the
表达式与
class of this represents the surrounding
这个类代表周围
scope and we can call get length on that
范围，我们可以调用获取长度
so these are the three different ways
所以这是三种不同的方式
that we can use method references right
我们可以使用方法引用正确
so now let's talk about lambda
所以现在让我们谈谈lambda
expression performance because there are
表达表现，因为有
some interesting things to understand
一些有趣的事情要理解
about that okay so the first thing is
关于那好吧，第一件事是
that as we've already kind of discussed
正如我们已经讨论过的那样
there is functional equivalence in terms
在功能上等效
of the three different types of way that
三种不同类型的方式中
we can represent a function in Java so
我们可以用Java表示一个函数
we could have a lambda expression like
我们可以有一个lambda表达式，例如
this so I want to say for each and then
所以我想为每个然后说
I'm just passing W as the the word for
我只是以W为代表
example and then printing it out okay so
例子，然后打印出来就可以了
that's a lambda expression being used we
那是一个lambda表达式被我们使用
also do that using a method reference
也可以使用方法参考
which you've already seen so we simply
您已经看过了，所以我们只需
say system dot out double colon print
说系统点出双冒号打印
line great
线大
functionally equivalent to the one above
在功能上等同于上述一种
and we could also do it with an
我们也可以用
anonymous in a class bit more verbose
课堂上的匿名者更加冗长
but exactly the same thing so now when
但现在完全一样
we're saying we have to create a new
我们是说我们必须创建一个新的
instance of a consumer of type string
字符串类型的使用者的实例
and we're going to override the accept
我们将覆盖接受
method and we're going to print out the
方法，我们将打印出
word right the important thing about
对吧，重要的事情
these is that none of these do anything
这是这些都不做任何事
different they all do exactly the same
不同，他们都做的完全一样
thing but how they compile is different
事情，但是他们如何编译是不同的
so we look at anonymous in the classes
所以我们在课堂上看匿名
the key thing here as the name suggests
顾名思义，这里的关键
is with that we're dealing with a class
是因为我们正在处理一个类
so when that code gets compiled the
因此，当该代码被编译时
compiler looks at what you've done and
编译器会查看您所做的事情，
it says ah you are trying to represent
它说啊，你试图代表
an interface but you can't do that
一个界面，但是你不能那样做
because you need a concrete class in
因为你需要一个具体的课程
order to generate an object of that type
为了生成该类型的对象
so the compiler will generate a class
所以编译器会生成一个类
for you and anonymous class and if
为你和匿名班，如果
you've got a class like foo then you're
你有一个像foo这样的课程，那么你就是
going to see a class which is named
会看到一个名为
something like food dollar 1 to
像食物美元1到
represent the anonymous in a class
代表班级中的匿名者
that's being used by food problem with
食物问题正在使用
this is you end up with what's called
这就是你最后的所谓
type of pollution so you're generating
污染的类型，因此您正在产生
lots more types in your application than
您的应用程序中的类型比
you really need what you really want is
你真的需要你真正想要的是
a function the other drawback to this is
功能的另一个缺点是
that because it is a class
那是因为这是一堂课
at runtime you have to load that class
在运行时，您必须加载该类
so there's an overhead in terms of
因此，在
loading the class there's an overhead in
加载课程有一个开销
terms of initializing that class and
初始化该类的条件，以及
then from the point of view of using it
然后从使用它的角度
it has to be instantiated that could
必须实例化
place an additional load on your heap
给您的堆增加额外的负担
space it could place an additional load
空间可能会增加额外的负载
on your garbage collector because you're
在你的垃圾收集器上，因为你
generating objects and that might result
生成对象，这可能会导致
in more garbage collection you actually
在更多的垃圾收集中，你实际上
want so there are a number of things
想要，所以有很多事情
where anonymous inner classes are not
没有匿名内部类的地方
necessarily the best way of doing it if
如果一定是最好的方法
you look at the lambda expressions
你看一下lambda表达式
because of this functional equivalence
由于这种功能上的等效
you could simply implement a lambda
你可以简单地实现一个lambda
expression as the equivalent anonymous
表示为等效的匿名
inner class so the compiler could take
内部类，以便编译器可以使用
that lambda expression convert it into
该lambda表达式将其转换为
an anonymous in a class piece of code
类代码中的匿名者
and then compile that in exactly the
然后将其完全
same way that you do in jdk 7 and
与在jdk 7和
earlier and in fact if you look at the
实际上，如果您先看一下
the way that lambdas were developed the
lambdas的开发方式
first implementation did exactly that
第一次实现确实做到了
so you've seen tactic sugar lambda
所以你看过战术糖lambda
expression convert it to anonymous in a
表达式将其转换为匿名
class compile it off you go
上课就编译吧
probably doing that way is you are
可能这样做是因为
forcing an inner class on your code
在代码上强制使用内部类
where you don't actually want it what
你实际上不想要什么
you really want is a function and the
您真正想要的是一个功能，
decision was obviously made not to him
显然是不给他的决定
not to have a function type in the
在...中没有功能类型
language but it would be nice if we
语言，但是如果我们
didn't have all the extra work involved
没有涉及所有额外的工作
trying to make a function type but then
试图做一个函数类型，但是
ending up with lots of extra classes so
最后有很多额外的课，所以
there has to be a better way of doing
必须有更好的方法
this and there is and the way that it's
这个和那里以及它的方式
done in jdk 8 is through the use of the
在jdk 8中完成的操作是通过使用
invokedynamic bytecode and method
invokedynamic字节码和方法
handles the reason behind this is that
处理这个背后的原因是
if you look at the history of
如果你看看历史
invokedynamic this is the first byte
invokedynamic这是第一个字节
code that was introduced in Java since
自Java以来​​引入的代码
it started and what it was goal was was
它开始了，目标是
to help languages that were being
帮助正在使用的语言
developed and compiled into byte codes
开发并编译成字节码
that weren't statically typed so if you
不是静态输入的，所以如果您
look at languages like JRuby for example
看看像JRuby这样的语言
not statically typed so you can change
非静态输入，因此您可以更改
the the types of parameters and return
参数的类型和返回
types of methods at runtime and in order
运行时和顺序中的方法类型
to do that with a statically typed
用静态类型做到这一点
virtual machine instruction set you
虚拟机指令集
to do a lot of extra work because you
做很多额外的工作，因为你
have to test everything before you call
打电话之前必须测试所有内容
the method you have to determine which
您必须确定哪种方法
method you're actually gonna be calling
您实际上要打电话的方法
so invoke dynamic was introduced in jar
所以在jar中引入了invoke dynamic
se7 to make life easier for compiler
se7使编译器的工作更轻松
writers who were generating code for the
编写代码的作家
JVM in JDK 8 he was actually used by
JDK 8中的JVM实际上是由他使用的
Java because the JDK 7 Java didn't use
Java，因为未使用JDK 7 Java
it so in JDK 8 lambda expressions used
在JDK 8 lambda表达式中使用
the invokedynamic bytecode and the idea
invokedynamic字节码和想法
behind this is to say ok we want to do
这背后是说好，我们想做
something in terms of using lambda
关于使用lambda的一些东西
expression but rather than fixing how we
表达，而不是固定我们的方式
do that into the compiled byte codes
做到这一点到编译的字节码
will use the invokedynamic bytecode and
将使用invokedynamic字节码和
we'll say leave the decision about how
我们将说出如何
this is implemented to runtime so then
这是在运行时实现的
the JVM can decide how it wants to do
JVM可以决定它想怎么做
the implementation of that lambda
该lambda的实现
expression when it's actually running
实际运行时的表情
and that way if new methods are found of
如果发现新方法
how to do that better performing ones
如何做到表现更好
it's very easy to change that we
我们很容易改变
couldn't change it in the JVM at runtime
运行时无法在JVM中更改它
rather than having to recompile your
而不需要重新编译
code and generate the new set of byte
代码并生成新的字节集
codes so as I tell you no fixed binary
我告诉你没有固定的二进制代码
format JVM can provide a different way
格式JVM可以提供不同的方式
of doing that now if we look at how
现在，如果我们看看如何
things work in terms of lambda
事情就lambda而言有效
compilation first thing is that the body
编译的第一件事就是身体
of the lambda expression has to be
lambda表达式的
converted into a method now I know of
转换成我现在知道的方法
I've already said you know it's a
我已经说过你知道这是一个
function it's not a method it's not
功能不是方法，不是
associated with the class but in order
与班级相关，但顺序
for it to work in terms of being used by
使其能够被使用
the the JVM it is converted into a
它转换成一个JVM
method in terms of its compilation now
现在就其编译方法
that's what's done in one of three ways
这是通过以下三种方式之一完成的
so the first is if you have a non
所以首先是如果你有一个非
capturing commander non capturing lambda
捕获指挥官不捕获lambda
is one where you don't reference any of
是您不参考任何
the variables from the surrounding scope
来自周围范围的变量
so you know if you're doing something
所以你知道你在做什么
like print line and well that's probably
像打印线，那可能是
not a good example but if you do
不是一个很好的例子，但是如果你这样做
something doesn't reference variables in
有些东西没有引用变量
the surrounding scope it's a non
周围的范围是一个非
capturing to do that it's very simple
捕捉到做到这一点非常简单
for the compiler because all it has to
对于编译器，因为它只需要
do is generate a new static method in
要做的是在中生成一个新的静态方法
the class where the lambda expression is
lambda表达式所在的类
being used where it passes the
在通过的地方使用
documents of the lambda expression as
Lambda表达式的文档为
arguments to the static method it
静态方法的参数
generates and the same return type
生成和相同的返回类型
so all it has to do is insert the body
所以要做的就是插入身体
of the lambda expression into that new
将lambda表达式转化为新的
method very simple conversion for a
方法非常简单的转换为
capturing lambda if it captures
捕获lambda（如果捕获）
variables like static variables and
像静态变量和
things like that then again it's fairly
这样的事情再一次是相当
straightforward to use because it will
易于使用，因为它将
the compiler will generate a static
编译器将生成一个静态
method the same way as we do for a non
方法与我们对非
capturing one but this time rather than
捕获一个，但是这次而不是
just passing the parameters that are the
只是传递参数
parameters of the lambda expression it
lambda表达式的参数吧
will prepend to those parameters any
将在任何参数之前添加这些参数
variables that you reference from the
您从中引用的变量
surrounding scope that's static so that
周围的范围是静态的，因此
way when the body of the expression runs
表达式主体运行的方式
it has the variables as instant those
它具有即时的变量
parameters they're being passed to the
参数被传递给
method so it is able to work in that way
方法，因此它能够以这种方式工作
the third form is where you have an
第三种形式是您拥有
instance capturing lambda so the lambda
实例捕获lambda，所以lambda
is actually referring to an object
实际上是指一个对象
rather than static very static methods
而不是静态的非常静态的方法
so in this case
所以在这种情况下
Rawdon creating a static method in the
Rawdon在
class in which the lambda expression is
lambda表达式所在的类
used it creates a truly synthetic method
用它创造了一种真正的合成方法
which is one associated with that
与之相关的一个
particular class and then when objects
特定的类，然后当对象
are created there's a method that's of
被创建有一种方法
that so in this case because it's a an
在这种情况下，因为这是一个
instance method in the class which uses
使用的类中的实例方法
a lambda expression it's able to refer
一个lambda表达式，它能够引用
to the surrounding object so it's able
到周围的物体上
to access the the variables that way so
以这种方式访问​​变量
this is how we generate the method one
这就是我们生成方法一的方式
of three ways we now have a method in
我们现在有三种方法
the class which is using the lambda
使用lambda的类
expression where you use the lambda
使用lambda的表达式
expression a call to invoke dynamic is
表示调用动态的表达式是
generated and what this is called is the
生成的，这就是所谓的
lambda factory so the idea is that you
lambda工厂，所以这个主意是
you make a call to the invoke dynamic
您调用动态调用
and that will return a reference to an
这将返回对
instance of an object whose type is the
类型为的对象的实例
functional interface that the lambda
lambda的功能接口
expression represents so that that kind
表情代表那种
of makes sense so we need some way of
很有道理，所以我们需要某种方式
getting a reference to the the object so
得到对对象的引用
that we can then call the method on it
然后我们可以在上面调用该方法
and in fact do that we also have a thing
实际上，我们也有一个东西
called the bootstrap method which is the
称为引导程序方法
lambda meta Factory and that uses the
lambda meta Factory，并使用
Java claimed or invoke lambda meta
Java声明或调用lambda元
Factory class the important thing about
工厂课重要的是
this is in terms of the the way that the
这是根据
lambda expressions work is the cool
lambda表达式工作很酷
science of the lambda expressions where
Lambda表达式科学在哪里
we use the meta Factory or if they
我们使用meta工厂，或者如果他们
evaluated in a lazy way that means that
懒惰地评估，这意味着
if you don't use that lambda expression
如果您不使用该lambda表达式
you don't have any overhead associated
您没有任何相关的间接费用
with it so this is quite an important
有了它，所以这很重要
thing from the point of view that unlike
从不同的角度来看
an enormous in a class where classes get
课堂上的巨大
created and classes will be loaded and
创建并加载类
things like that from the point of view
从这样的角度来看
if you don't use a lambda expression
如果您不使用Lambda表达式
then you don't have the overhead of
那你就没有
actually calling the lambda Mehta
实际上叫lambda Mehta
factory so it's it's ignored which means
工厂，所以它被忽略，这意味着
you get better performance by using
通过使用您可以获得更好的性能
lambda expressions in that sense the
从这个意义上讲，lambda表达式
next thing is if we look at the
接下来的事情是，如果我们看
differences in terms of implementation
实施方面的差异
between lambdas and anonymous inner
在lambda和匿名内部之间
classes and you can break out what both
上课，您可以了解两者
of these things do into three distinct
这些事情分为三个不同的
sections in the case of lambdas the
在lambdas的情况下
first thing is how you link to the
首先是您如何链接到
reference to the the class which is
引用的类是
going to give you the method which is
要给你的方法是
going to be called as the lambda
被称为lambda
expression body for an anonymous in a
匿名中的表达主体
class the equivalent of that is loading
类相当于加载
the class that you need to call the
您需要调用的课程
method in order to execute the anonymous
为了执行匿名方法
in a class method now from the point of
现在从一个类方法
view of comparing these two Oracle did
比较这两个Oracle的观点
quite a lot of performance analysis and
大量的性能分析和
there's a there's a video online that
有一个在线视频
you can find which talks about this
您可以找到有关此的话题
thing in quite some length so the team
在相当长的时间内，所以团队
in Russia did a lot of work on this and
在俄罗斯做了很多工作，
what they found was that if you look at
他们发现的是，如果你看
the kind of comparison of these two from
这两种的比较从
a lambda point of view once you get
一旦获得，就可以得出lambda的观点
through to what's called the hot path so
通过所谓的热路径
once everything is kind of settled down
一旦一切都安顿下来
and you use these things a few times
你会用这些东西几次
linkage in class loading is about the
类加载中的链接是关于
same so so the the effect of using
一样，所以使用的效果
lambda expressions performance wise is
lambda表达式的性能明智的是
about the same as anonymous inner
与匿名内部大致相同
classes so you don't get any advantage
类，所以你没有任何优势
for using either
用于使用
but from the cold path which is where
但是从寒冷的道路上
you start up so if you're only using a
您会启动，因此，如果您仅使用
lambda expression a few times obviously
lambda表达几次
that's going through the cold path
经历了冷酷的道路
rather than the hot path then lambdas
而不是热门路径，然后是lambdas
win so lambdas actually have much better
赢了，所以lambdas实际上要好得多
performance in terms of the first
在第一方面的表现
startup bit because class loading is a
启动位，因为类加载是
lot heavier wake operation than the
唤醒操作比
linkage that you need for the call site
呼叫站点所需的链接
of the lambda expression so the net
Lambda表达式的净值
effect of that is that lambdas win
这样做的结果是lambdas获胜
because in the first startup bit they're
因为在第一个启动位中
better and then once you get to the sort
更好，然后一旦您进入排序
of stable state they're about the same
处于稳定状态时，它们大致相同
as anonymous inner classes second part
作为匿名内部类第二部分
is capture and instantiation so capture
是捕获和实例化，所以捕获
for lambdas how we deal with captured
对于lambdas，我们如何处理捕获
variables instantiation for the
的变量实例化
anonymous in a class and what they found
在课堂上匿名，他们发现了什么
there was if you look at the two they
如果你看两个
perform about the same if you're using a
如果您使用的是
single threaded environment so both will
单线程环境，所以两者都会
be about roughly equal if you start
如果开始的话，大约相等
using multiple threads and you've got
使用多个线程，您已经
more cause in terms of what you're doing
您所做的事情更多
with though that particular part then
尽管那部分
lambdas will win so lambdas perform a
lambdas会赢，所以lambdas会执行
lot better as the number of threads
线程数更好
number of cores increases anonymous
内核数增加匿名
inner classes don't get the same benefit
内部类不会获得相同的好处
in terms of the Stan she ation addresses
就斯坦语而言
of their the capturing the other thing
他们捕捉另一件事
that we was found about the way that
我们被发现的方式
lambdas work in comparison to anonymous
与匿名相比，lambdas的工作
inner classes is that if you have a
内部类是，如果你有一个
non-static anonymous in a class then you
非静态匿名类，然后您
actually need 50 percent more space to
实际需要50％以上的空间
represent a reference to a captured
表示对捕获的引用
variable than you do in a lambda
比在lambda中可变
expression so again this is a small
再次表达，这是一个很小的
thing but it means that lambdas again
东西，但这意味着又是lambdas
come out on a head in terms of
就...而言
performance and then the last bit is
性能，最后一点是
where both of the different ways of
两种不同的方式
doing things invoke the method since
服务器调用该方法，因为
they're doing the same thing they're
他们在做同样的事情
invoking a method there's no difference
调用方法没有区别
between those two so overall what was
在这两个之间，总的来说
found was that lambda expressions come
发现是lambda表达式来的
out on top in terms of performance which
在性能方面领先
is what you would hope now in terms of
您现在希望的是
like rules of thumb non capturing
就像经验法则无法捕捉
lambdas automatically optimized just the
lambdas会自动优化
way they work is that they're they're
他们工作的方式是
better in terms of optimization second
在优化第二方面更好
thing is that method references are
问题是方法引用是
slightly more up
稍微多一点
the reason for that is that as I
原因是因为我
described to you earlier one of the
向您介绍了其中一项
first thing that has to happen where
必须发生的第一件事
lambda is compiled is you have to
lambda已编译，您必须
generate a new method which has the body
产生一种具有主体的新方法
of the lambda expression in it if you're
其中的lambda表达式
using a method reference you don't need
使用不需要的方法引用
to do that because you already have a
这样做是因为您已经有一个
method reference so you don't need to
方法参考，因此您不需要
create a new one to put a call to
创建一个新的来拨打电话
another method in it so the compiler
另一个方法，所以编译器
will simply ignore having to create a
只会忽略必须创建一个
new method and we'll just use the method
新方法，我们将只使用该方法
reference directly so that way if you
直接引用，这样，如果您
use a method reference it's actually
使用实际上是一个方法引用
more efficient than using the same code
比使用相同的代码更有效
as a lambda explicit lambda expression
作为lambda显式lambda表达式
the other thing that they found in terms
他们发现的另一件事
of doing their analysis was that tiered
做他们的分析是分层的
compilation gave better results with
编译给出了更好的结果
lambda expressions now the point is that
lambda表达式现在的重点是
tier compilation is turned on by default
默认情况下，层编译处于打开状态
so the advice really is don't use -
所以建议真的不使用-
tiered compilation don't turn tier
分层编译不分层
compilation off if you want better
如果您想要更好的编译
performance from your lambda expressions
lambda表达式的效果
right so that's performance okay so now
对，所以表现还可以，所以现在
we've had the interesting and useful
我们有有趣而有用的
section now we're going to move on to
现在，我们将继续
the interesting but also useful section
有趣但又有用的部分
right so the idea here is how far can we
对，所以这里的想法是我们能走多远
take lambdas now I have to give credit
现在我要拿lambda
to somebody else for giving me
给别人给我
inspiration on this because it was last
因为这是最后的灵感
year at conference in Switzerland there
年在瑞士的会议上
was somebody called Jarek or an attached
是一个叫Jarek的人
key who did a presentation on lambda
谁在lambda上做演讲的关键
expressions I sat there and I watched it
我坐在那里看的表情
he did it in an IDE which was was just
他在一个IDE中做到了
blew me away
吓死我了
so he did it into IDE and he kind of did
所以他把它做到了IDE，他做了
all this this Java on the screen I
屏幕上所有这些Java
looked it I thought I have no idea what
看起来我以为我不知道
he's doing and I had to think about it a
他在干，我不得不考虑一下
lot and I had to go and sort of I talked
很多，我不得不走了，我说话了
to him afterwards and I we kind of
之后给他，我有点
chatted about it and I and so this is
我和它聊天，所以这是
this is where we come from right so the
这是我们来自正确的地方，所以
first thing is we call all these things
首先是我们将所有这些称为
lambda expressions why do we call them
lambda表达式为什么我们称它们为
lambda expressions and the reason is
lambda表达式，原因是
because of Alonzo Church so Alonzo
因为阿隆佐教堂所以阿隆佐
Church came up with the idea of lambda
教会提出了lambda的想法
calculus
结石
back in the middle of the 1930s so
早在1930年代中期
clearly you kind of think to yourself
显然你对自己想
well what does that have to do with Java
好，这与Java有什么关系
which didn't actually come out until
直到实际上才出来
1995 so you know 60 years later Java
1995年，您知道60年后的Java
comes out
出来
then it's another what is it like almost
那几乎是另一种感觉
20 years before we get lambda
拉姆达之前20年
expressions now the thing is that alonso
现在的表情是阿隆索
chose the lambda calculus was a
选择了λ演算是
mathematical way of representing any
数学表示方式
sort of way of processing things with
一种处理事物的方式
functions and so the interesting thing
功能等等有趣的事情
about Alonzo Church was he was also this
关于阿隆佐教堂，他也是这个
supervisor for Alan Turing when Alan
艾伦·图灵当主管
Turing did his PhD in Cambridge so this
图灵在剑桥获得博士学位
is the kind of interesting connection
是一种有趣的联系
between lambda expressions which is
在lambda表达式之间
functional programming now ensuring who
函数式编程现在可以确保谁
obviously did a lot of work on the
显然，在
design of the modern computer so this is
现代计算机的设计，这是
where we get into what I call exploding
我们进入所谓的爆炸
head lambdas as Java programmers we are
作为Java程序员，我们是lambda头
very much accustomed to imperative
非常习惯命令
programming so we like to deal with
编程，所以我们喜欢处理
loops and we very much like to deal with
循环，我们非常想处理
state so we have variables in our
状态，所以我们有变量
program we have for loops we have while
我们有for循环的程序
loops and so on but the problem is that
循环等等，但是问题是
functional programming is not imperative
函数式编程不是必须的
so I like to ask this question and so
所以我想问这个问题
everybody here's a job program I'm sure
我敢肯定，这是一个工作计划
so who would also consider themselves a
所以谁还会认为自己是
functional programmer yes you see
功能程序员，是的，您看到了
there's a few people but not everybody
有几个人，但不是每个人
and that's really quite telling I all
这真的告诉了我所有人
the audiences I'm I talk to this is very
我正在与之交谈的观众非常
common there are a few people who have
常见的有一些人
done functional programming in other
完成其他功能编程
languages but a lot of Java programmers
语言，但很多Java程序员
are not functional programmers and it
不是函数式程序员，它
does take a different way of thinking
确实采取了不同的思维方式
about things to actually do functional
关于实际起作用的事情
programming properly I would believe you
正确编程，我相信你
I learned that the hard way if you came
我了解到如果你来的话很难
to my streams and lambdas talk this
在我的小溪和Lambdas上谈论这个
morning with Stuart Marx you'll see how
与斯图尔特·马克思的早晨，你会看到
badly I can write code using functional
糟糕的是我可以使用功能编写代码
programming anyway so the interesting
编程还是很有趣
thing about lambda expressions and
关于lambda表达式和
lambda calculus is that lambda calculus
lambda演算就是lambda演算
and chewing machines are completely
和咀嚼机是完全
equivalent now Turing machines if you
现在等效的图灵机
have a Turing complete language Java C
具有图灵完整语言Java C
C++ even javascript is Turing complete
C ++甚至JavaScript都完成了图灵
then any problem that can be solved by a
那么任何可以解决的问题
computer can be solved in that language
电脑可以用这种语言解决
lambda calculus is equivalent in terms
Lambda微积分在术语上是等效的
of the way that they work to the Turing
他们在图灵工作的方式
machine so that means that any problem
机器，这意味着任何问题
that you can solve with computation
您可以通过计算解决
can be solved using lambda calculus but
可以使用lambda演算来解决，但是
it will give you a headache believe me
这会让你头疼相信我
at least it did me and I'll explain a
至少对我有用，我会解释
bit more of that as we go through so the
随着我们经历的更多
idea now is what can we do in Java if we
现在的想法是，如果我们
only use lambda expressions so we're not
只使用lambda表达式，所以我们不
going to use any primitive types we're
将要使用的任何原始类型
not going to use any operators we're not
不会使用任何我们不会的运算符
going to use any now we're not gonna use
现在将要使用的任何东西我们都不会使用
any objects either so literally only
任何对象
going to use lambda expressions and
将使用lambda表达式
we'll have one functional interface we
我们将有一个功能界面
have to have a functional interface in
必须有一个功能接口
order to create a lambda expression so
为了创建一个lambda表达式
what can we do with this right so the
我们可以用这项权利做什么？
first thing is our functional interface
首先是我们的功能界面
so we'll call it very originally a
所以我们最初将其称为
lambda okay and lambda is going to have
lambda好的，lambda将会有
one method one abstract method called
一种方法一种抽象方法称为
apply apply takes as a parameter a
apply Apply将参数a
lambda expression and returns a lambda
lambda表达式并返回一个lambda
expression so that way we can chain them
表达，以便我们可以将它们链接起来
together very easily good so now we have
在一起非常容易，所以现在我们有了
to start off and think about how can we
开始思考，我们如何
do things in Java if we're not only as
如果我们不仅在Java中做事情，
primitive types we're not going to use
我们将不使用的原始类型
operators well the first thing is we
操作员很好，第一件事是我们
need a lambda expression to represent my
需要一个lambda表达式来代表我
density so identity is where you pass
密度，所以身份是您通过的地方
something and you get the same thing
和你得到相同的东西
back great so we can represent and we
回到伟大，所以我们可以代表，我们
can create a lambda expression called
可以创建一个名为的lambda表达式
identity and that returns a lambda
身份，并返回一个lambda
expression where you pass it a parameter
您在其中传递参数的表达式
and it returns the same parameter so it
它返回相同的参数，所以它
just gives you back what you give it so
就是把你给的东西还给你
far so simple and in red I've actually
如此简单和红色，我实际上
used the the lambda notation because
使用lambda表示法是因为
sometimes he actually gets a lot easier
有时候他实际上变得容易得多
to understand in the land of notation
在表示法领域理解
than it does the the Java code right so
而不是Java代码，所以
we have a lambda identity for the first
我们第一个拥有lambda身份
couple slides I'm also going to show you
几张幻灯片，我也要告诉你
the equivalent anonymous in a class
类中的等效匿名
because sometimes that makes it a little
因为有时候这会使它有点
bit easier to understand so in this case
有点容易理解，所以在这种情况下
we're creating a lambda called identity
我们正在创建一个称为身份的lambda
which is a new lambda which then has an
这是一个新的lambda，然后有一个
implementation of the apply method which
apply方法的实现
takes a lambda X and returns X okay all
接受一个λX并返回X好吧
good so next we need some primitive
好，所以接下来我们需要一些原始的
types so we're gonna create boolean
类型，所以我们要创建布尔值
representations true and false so we'll
表示是非，所以我们将
start with false and in this case false
以false开头，在这种情况下为false
is a lambda expression which always
是一个lambda表达式，它总是
returns the lambda expression which we
返回我们的lambda表达式
have for identity
有身份
okay so we're getting a little bit more
好吧，我们会得到更多
complicated so we have a lambda
复杂，所以我们有一个lambda
expression F which returns another
表达式F返回另一个
lambda expression which is the identity
lambda表达式是身份
lambda expression and again if we just
lambda表达式，如果我们只是
look at the equivalent anonymous inner
看看等效的匿名内部
class we've just got two layers of
上课我们只有两层
lambda expression there so nothing
lambda表达式在那里什么都没有
terribly exciting but I'm not going to
非常令人兴奋，但我不会
show you any more anonymous inner
向您显示更多匿名内部
classes because it does get way way too
上课，因为它确实也有办法
much code the opposite boolean false is
相反的布尔假的很多代码是
clearly boolean true so in this case
显然是布尔型，所以在这种情况下
we'll have a lambda expression which
我们将有一个lambda表达式
returns a lambda which is never going to
返回一个永远不会去的lambda
be identity so in this case we can say
是身份，在这种情况下，我们可以说
okay so it's the opposite of true the
好吧，这与真实的相反
opposite force is true great so we have
相反的力量真的很棒，所以我们有
an lambda expression which does that so
一个lambda表达式这样做
now we've got billions right next we
现在我们接下来有数十亿美元
need numbers so there are things called
需要数字，所以有些事情叫做
church numerals church numeral we can we
教堂数字教堂数字我们可以
can sort of take some mathematical
可以有点数学
inspiration here and we can say that the
灵感在这里，我们可以说
identity for addition is 0 if you add a
如果添加一个标识，则添加标识为0
subtract 0 from any number you get the
从任何数字中减去0
same number back so it's the same as an
后面的数字相同，因此与
identity we already know what the lambda
身份，我们已经知道lambda是什么
expression for identity is so what we'll
身份的表达就是我们要做的
do in this case is will use the lambda
在这种情况下，将使用lambda
expression for identity to represent the
表示身份的表达式
number 0 that makes sense it's also kind
数字0很有意思
of logical from the point of view of
从...的角度来看
using our boolean true and false if you
如果您使用我们的布尔值true和false
think about C programming C language if
考虑一下C编程C语言
you if you don't see in C there isn't a
如果您没有在C中看到您，则不会
boolean type so if you evaluate an if
布尔类型，因此如果您评估if
statement then the the false value is 0
语句，则假值为0
true is anything other than 0 so in this
true是除0以外的任何值，因此在此
case true is the same as the identity
区分大小写与身份相同
expression so it's also the yes so we
表达，所以也是，所以我们
end up with 0 and so it kind of ties
最终以0结束，因此有种联系
together great the other thing is that
在一起很棒的另一件事是
you can think of it in this way that the
你可以这样想
function f is being applied to the
函数f正在应用于
lambda expression 0 times now you might
lambda表达式0次，现在可能
look at mango okay what does that mean
看芒果好吧，那是什么意思
if I point isn't 0 times but it becomes
如果我指的不是0次，而是
clearer if we look at 1 okay so the
如果我们看1还好，那么
lambda expression for 1 is a lambda
1的lambda表达式是lambda
expression where we take X and then we
表达式，我们取X，然后我们
apply X to the function f that we're
将X应用于函数f
passing like I say this already starts
像我所说的已经过去了
to get a little as a Java program it was
得到一点Java程序
already starting to get a little bit
已经开始有点
complicated here so that's what we did
这里很复杂，这就是我们所做的
we have apply the function f to X and
我们将函数f应用于X并
make that part of our lambda expression
成为我们lambda表达的一部分
and the key thing here is if you look at
关键是如果你看
lambda calculus lambda calculus doesn't
lambda演算lambda演算不
use loops so we would never use a for
使用循环，所以我们永远不会使用for
loop in lambda calculus lambda calculus
Lambda演算中的循环Lambda演算中的循环
does things repeatedly by in effect
反复做事
recursively calling the same function so
递归调用相同的函数
if we look at the lambda expression for
如果我们看一下lambda表达式
2 what we do is we apply the function
2我们要做的就是应用功能
recursively twice so now we have X goes
递归两次，所以现在我们有X去
to F dot apply of F dot apply of X great
到F点的应用X的F点的应用
set and you can continue with that as
设置，您可以继续
many times as you like to represent
你想代表很多次
numbers greater than 2 I'm not going to
大于2的数字我不会
do that because I think twos enough you
这样做是因为我认为你已经足够了
get the idea right now we need to look
现在知道这个主意，我们需要看看
at how we can do some mathematics so how
我们如何去做一些数学
about if we want to increase the number
关于我们是否要增加数量
that we have by one well that's actually
实际上，我们拥有一口井
not too difficult because if you think
不太困难，因为如果您认为
about it what we need to do is we simply
关于它，我们需要做的就是
need to apply the function to that again
需要再次将该功能应用于该功能
so the the lambda notation shows that is
所以lambda表示法表明
that way and in terms of a successor
这样，就后继者而言
lambda expression we end up with n which
lambda表达式以n结束
is our number and then we want to apply
是我们的电话号码，然后我们要申请
the function f to that one more time so
函数f到那一次
we get F dot apply of n dot apply of F
我们得到F点适用n点适用F
dot apply of X okay so the successor is
X的点适用，所以后继者是
fairly straightforward if we simply want
如果我们只想简单地说
to apply that function one more time
再次应用该功能
the predecessor a little bit more tricky
前辈比较棘手
because what we're doing is we're
因为我们在做的是
actually removing one call to the
实际上删除了对
function so that that makes life a
功能，使生活成为
little bit harder and I'm not going to
有点难，我不会
explain this I'm just going to show you
解释一下，我只是要告诉你
what it is
这是什么
so that's the lambda note that's the
这就是lambda音符
lambda notation forever because then we
永远是lambda表示法，因为那时我们
start getting all sorts of extra letters
开始得到各种各样的多余字母
involved so there's G H and U and X and
因此涉及GH和U以及X
the equivalent Java code becomes this so
等效的Java代码变成这样
it becomes quite sort of nasty in terms
它变得很讨厌
of our gates n F X and apply GJ over
我们的大门n FX并在
that we're not going to use that so I
我们不会使用它，所以我
figured that that that's some rather
认为那是相当
complicated if you really follow it
如果您真的遵循它，将会很复杂
through it does actually work and
通过它确实有效，
guarantee that so then let's look at how
保证，那么让我们看看如何
we can add two numbers together almost
我们几乎可以将两个数字相加
into the the kind of bit where we're
变成我们所处的那种
going to do something interesting so
要做一些有趣的事情
addition is simply repeated incrementing
加法只是重复递增
so if I want to add n to M it's the same
所以如果我想在M上加上n
as saying add 1 to M n times so you
就像说加1到M n次，所以你
already know how to add 1 to a function
已经知道如何向函数加1
so all we're going to do in this case is
所以我们在这种情况下要做的就是
add 1 to the function n times so you end
n次加1到函数结束
up this slightly more complex way of
这种更复杂的方式
doing things that we've got m n FX and
做我们有百万外汇和
all the applies right subtract which
所有适用权减去
again we won't bother with going into
再次，我们不会去打扰
too much detail we'll use the
过多的细节我们将使用
predecessor function to to shrink down
缩小功能
some of the code but we can do the same
一些代码，但我们可以做同样的事情
thing of repeatedly applying the
反复应用
decrement operation to decorate ok so
递减操作来装饰好吧
then I thought right we want to do
然后我想我们想做的对
something simple with lambdas let's add
用lambdas做些简单的事情，让我们添加一下
2 plus 2 only using lambdas right so we
2加2仅使用lambdas，所以我们
know the lambda for 2 is apply the
知道2的lambda适用
function twice recursively and so that
函数两次递归
that's that straightforward
就是这么简单
F X F dot apply of F dot apply base and
FXF点应用F点应用基础和
we know that the lambda expression for
我们知道lambda表达式用于
plus is MN F X but a lot of up right we
加号是MN FX，但我们有很多建议
need to combine these two and
需要结合这两个
interestingly we can do that by saying a
有趣的是，我们可以这样说
simple thing and this is Java code
很简单，这是Java代码
lambda 4 equals Plus which is our lambda
lambda 4等于Plus，这就是我们的lambda
expression and then we apply to that 2
表达式，然后我们将其应用于2
and we apply to that too so we're
而且我们也对此适用
calling it recursively twice with two
递归两次调用两次
values too and if you kind of write that
也有价值观，如果你写那种
out just as the the mathematics you end
就像你结束的数学一样
up with 4 equals plus 2 2 and this is
等于4等于2 2
what's called polish notation I don't
所谓的波兰语符号
know about you know
知道你知道
for those of you old enough to remember
对于你们这些足以记住的人
like very early calculate P calculators
像很早就计算出P计算器
I think used a reverse polish so this is
我认为使用了反向抛光，所以这是
forward polish rather than reverse
正向抛光而不是反向抛光
polish notation but you get the idea
波兰符号，但你明白了
that in order to add things we can we
为了添加东西，我们可以
can actually do it only using lambda
实际上只能使用lambda做到这一点
expressions so we can say lambda for it
表达式，所以我们可以说lambda
was plus dot apply to apply to write how
是加号申请写申请如何
do we know that that works okay so this
我们知道那行得通吗
is where like it's interesting because
是有趣的地方，因为
what we'll do is we'll follow through
我们将要做的是
the stages of how to actually show this
如何实际显示这个阶段
and I have to say that one of the things
我必须说，其中一件事
that when I was doing this I was sitting
当我这样做的时候，我坐在
at the table and my son who was 10 at
在桌子上，我儿子十岁
the time he came down me scribbling out
他跌倒的时候我在外面乱涂乱画
stuff and I try and work things out and
东西，我尝试解决问题，
he said to me what are you doing daddy I
他对我说你爸爸我在做什么
said I'm trying to work out what two
说我正在尝试找出两个
plus two he looks at you looks at me
再加上两个他看着你看着我
like I was stupid he said well that's
就像我很蠢，他说的很好
easy daddy it's four
易爸爸，四岁
so I said I'm trying to use lambda
所以我说我想用lambda
calculus for this so I showed him that
为此，我向他展示了
the writing that I was looking goes no
我一直在看的写作没有
no it's four so anyway so so what we'll
不，现在是四个，所以我们会
do is we'll take our Edition lambda
要做的是，我们将采用Edition lambda
expression so we have M and we have n
表达式，所以我们有M而我们有n
that we're going to add together so in
我们将要加在一起
the case of M we're going to replace M
在M的情况下，我们将替换M
with the lambda expression for two so we
有两个的lambda表达式，所以我们
get a slightly longer lambda expression
获得稍长的lambda表达式
I've highlighted in red where we replace
我用红色突出显示了我们要替换的地方
M with the lambda expression for two so
M用lambda表达式表示两个
we also take em away from the front
我们也把他们从前面带走
because now we're in effect applying
因为现在我们实际上正在申请
that to the the function and then what
该功能，然后什么
we need to do is the same thing for n so
我们需要为n做同样的事情
n is 2 as well so we'll replace the N
n也为2，所以我们替换N
that we have there with the lambda
我们在那里有lambda
expression for 2 and we end up with
2的表达式，最后得到
quite a long lambda expression but it
Lambda表达式很长，但它
doesn't quite look like for yet so we
看起来还不太适合，所以我们
have to do some reduction on this so if
必须对此做一些减少，如果
we switched that what we now need to say
我们切换了我们现在需要说的
is okay so we've got FX and then we've
没关系，所以我们有外汇，然后我们
got this we've got this bit here in blue
有了这个，我们在这里有了蓝色
where we're saying f is the lambda
我们在说f是lambda
expression which is returning X goes to
返回X的表达式转到
F dot apply of F dot apply X dot apply
F点适用F点适用X点适用
of F the nice thing about that is that F
F的好处是F
is we're applying F to that but F is the
是我们正在应用F，但F是
variable if you like so it's quite a
如果您愿意的话，可以选择一个变量
simple reduction we just in essence
简单的还原，我们实质上
off the apply and remove F so now yet X
关闭应用并删除F，所以现在X
goes to F dot apply of F dot apply of X
转到F点X的F点应用
and if we do the same thing here we've
如果我们在这里做同样的事情，我们已经
got a lambda expression here we've got F
这里有一个lambda表达式，我们有F
and we want to apply F to that lambda
我们想将F应用于该lambda
expression then we can do the same thing
表达，然后我们可以做同样的事情
which reduces down so we get X goes to F
减少，所以我们得到X到F
dot apply of F dot of 5x then what we
点应用F的5x点，那么我们
need to do is we take that which has
我们需要做的是
been condensed down but we still got F
被压缩，但我们仍然得到F
goes to X goes to X goes to our f of
转到X转到X转到我们的f
apply and so on but we need to apply
申请等等，但我们需要申请
this whole blue and it's actually in
这整个蓝色，它实际上在
within the apply we're going to apply X
在申请范围内，我们将申请X
again X is an easy one to to eliminate
再次，X是一个容易消除的
because it's the same variable so we end
因为它是相同的变量，所以我们结束
up with F dot apply of F dot apply of X
由F点套用X的F点套用
but now things are a little bit more
但现在事情有点多了
complicated because we have to apply
复杂，因为我们必须申请
where we have X the whole of this lambda
我们有X整个这个lambda
expression F dot apply of F dot apply X
表达式F点适用F点适用X
and that reduces down to yes so we get
然后减少到是，所以我们得到
that we reduce that X changes yes so
我们减少X改变是的
then we reduce that and we end up with F
然后我们减少它，最后得到F
goes to X goes to F that apply of F that
转到X转到F
apply of F that apply of F that apply of
F的适用F的适用F的适用
X which is four we have proved that two
X是四个，我们证明了两个
plus two is four and we've shown that we
加两个是四，我们证明了我们
can do it only new zealander expressions
只能做到新的热情表达
like I say did take me quite a while to
就像我说过花了我一段时间
get that straight in my head so just to
弄直我的脑袋
summarize then lambda expressions very
然后非常总结lambda表达式
useful very powerful a nice succinct way
非常有用的非常简洁的方法
to represent behavior so you can pass it
代表行为，以便您可以通过
as a variable you can assign to a
作为变量，您可以分配给
variable capacitor as a parameter
可变电容器作为参数
better performance than anonymous inner
比匿名内部更好的性能
classes so if you're thinking you know
上课，所以如果您认为自己知道
in terms of like performance programming
就类似性能编程而言
then lambda expressions are better way
那么lambda表达式是更好的方法
of doing things than nonnamous inner
做事比不内在的内在
classes method references are even
类方法的引用是偶数
slightly better than a then lambda
比后来的lambda好一点
expression explicit lambda expressions
表达式显式lambda表达式
and as I say here you can use them weird
正如我在这里所说，您可以使用它们很奇怪
in wonderful ways but I certainly
以奇妙的方式，但我当然
wouldn't recommend trying to write all
不建议尝试全部写
your code only using lambda expressions
您的代码仅使用lambda表达式
if you want to do two plus two in Java
如果您想用Java做2加2
use the primitive int type use the plus
使用原始int类型使用加号
operator much much easier more
操作员要容易得多
information like I said my inspiration
信息就像我说的那样
came from the Eric's presentation
来自埃里克的演讲
there's a video of him doing this at
有一个视频，他在
devoxx in a box in Zurich and there's
devoxx在苏黎世的一个盒子里，
also what Jarek based his work on which
Jarek的工作基于什么
was Dickson Yang's blog who works for
是Dickson Yang的博客，为
Microsoft and he did this in C shock so
微软和他在C震惊中做到了这一点，所以
it's a similar kind of thing but he's
这是类似的事情，但他是
got a lot more detail about how this all
关于这一切的更多细节
kind of works out so with that thank you
这样的工作，所以谢谢
very much
非常
[Applause]
[掌声]